（岡部倫太郎(おかべりんたろう)）なぜだ？
Why?
What's going on?
どうなっている？
The entire culture of cute is gone from Akiba?
アキバから“萌(も)え”がすべて
消失してしまったというのか？
Okarin, wait up!
（椎名(しいな)まゆり）オカリン 待ってよ
（橋田 至(はしだ いたる)）オカリン オカ…
Okarin!
What's wrong?
（まゆり）どうしちゃったの？
Where's the Toranoana? The Animate?
（岡部）
「とらのあな」も「アニメイト」も
どこにいったのだ？
The Mandarake? The Gamers?
「まんだらけ」や
「ゲーマーズ」は？
What are you talking about, Okarin?
（まゆり）
何言ってるの？ オカリン
Why would those be in Akiba?
そんなの
アキバにあるわけないよ
That's why I'm going to Nakano to get my comics.
だから まゆしぃは
中野(なかの)まで同人誌を…
Mayuri,
まゆり お前―
you work part-time at May Queen, right?
「メイクイーン」で
バイトしていたよな？
May Queen?
（まゆり）
「メイクイーン」って？
May Queen Meow Meow!
（岡部）
「メイクイーンニャンニャン」だ！
Impossible...
バカな…
Feyris was the one who requested to bring the culture of cute to Akiba.
（フェイリス）アキバに萌え文化を
取り入れるように―
お願いしたのは
フェイリスなのニャ
She sent a D-mail, preventing that from ever happening?
（岡部）
それを否定するＤメールを
過去に送ったのか…
With just one message,
たった１通のメールで―
the whole town changed.
町が まるまる
改変されるなんて…
～
Chaos Theory
Homeostasis
（阿万音鈴羽(あまねすずは)）あ…
It's hard to believe that May Queen used to be here.
（岡部）
「メイクイーン」があった場所とは
とても思えん
（橋田）
“メイクイーン”って
ジャガイモ？
May Queen? Is that a potato?
夏はジャガバタより
つけ麺っしょ
During summer, I prefer noodles to potatoes.
It isn't a potato...
（岡部）だから
ジャガイモの話ではなく…
「メイクイーン」がなければ―
If May Queen never existed, then how did we meet Feyris?
俺たちはフェイリスと
どうやって知り合ったんだ？
Well, it's thanks to potato ramen that we met her.
ま… 確かに フェイリスたんと
知り合えたのは―
ジャガバタラーメンの
おかげだけど
What do you mean?
（岡部）どういうことだ？
忘れたん？
You don't remember?
On the day of the Rai-Net Tournament in Ikebukuro,
池袋(いけぶくろ)で
雷(らい)ネットの大会があった日―
お昼に食べた
ジャガバタラーメンのせいで―
I got sick from the potato ramen I had for lunch,
おなか壊して―
（橋田）僕がリタイヤして…
（岡部）う… それで？
so I withdrew.
And then?
代わりにオカリンとまゆ氏が
参戦して―
Mayushii and you entered as a pair,
and you went up against Feyris.
そのときの対戦相手が
フェイリスたん
You totally lost,
オカリンたちは
惨敗したんだけど―
そのときから
まゆ氏とフェイリスたんは―
but Mayushii and Feyris became friends.
お友達になったんしょ
（岡部）なるほど
I see.
Look, look, Ruka.
（まゆり）
見て見て るかちゃん
I bought this cosplayer's photobook yesterday in Nakano!
昨日 中野で買った
レイヤーさん写真集
（漆原(うるしばら)るか）うわあ
So cute...
The past changed, but our relationships haven't?
（岡部）過去は変わっても
結果的に現在の人間関係は
変わってないということか
You seem to have lots of time
盆休みだというのに
ずいぶん暇そうだな
on your hands with this bon festival, lab member girls.
ラボメンガールズよ
お邪魔してます
Hello there.
ほら カワイイでしょう
Look! Cute, huh?
おおっ
ブラチューのセドナコス！
Hey! It's Sedona from Blood Tune!
（まゆり）
作り込みすごいでしょ
水着もあるよ
It's really detailed!
There's a swimsuit version too.
憧れるなあ
I wish I could be like that.
I don't have those proportions.
僕 こんなに
スタイルよくないから
（まゆり）大丈夫
“貧乳は正義”なんだよ
It's okay!
Being flat isn't a crime!
（牧瀬紅莉栖(まきせくりす)）
ぶはっ！ コホッ コホッ
I know!
（まゆり）
そうだ！ 今度ラボメンのみんなで
海に行こうよ
Why not take all the lab members,
and go to the beach?
紅莉栖ちゃんも一緒に
With Kurisu too!
Everyone, wear your school swimsuits, okay?
（橋田）全員 スク水でオケ？
変態と海水浴なんてっ！
I'm not going swimming with a pervert.
（まゆり）ええーっ
Um, well... I mean, if it's just the girls,
ああ… つまりその―
女子メンバー限定ってことなら―
I'd love to!
喜んで参加させてもらう
ってことで
（岡部）フハハッ
Why not be honest, Christina?
素直になったらどうだ？
クリスティーナ
私は でん部の蒙古斑(もうこはん)を
見られたくないので―
You don't want anyone to see the mole on your rear,
so you can't go. Right?
一緒には行けませんと…
There's no mole!
（紅莉栖）なっ！
蒙古斑なんてないわよ
And if it's just the girls,
それに そもそも
女子メンバー限定ならば―
then Rukako can't go.
そこの るか子も無理ではないか
はっ？ なんでよ？
Huh? Why not?
いや この前 教えただろ
I told you earlier, right?
That Rukako's actually a guy.
るか子は正真正銘の男だと
えっ？
あっ
なっ！
へ？
You're a real jerk, you know?
（紅莉栖）最悪ね あんた
How can you call a girl a guy?
女の子に向かって
男呼ばわりなんて
（まゆり）そういうこと言うの
まゆしぃ好きじゃないな
Mayushii doesn't like it when you say stuff like that.
Isn't that really mean?
（橋田）さすがにマズくね？
ちょ ちょ… ちょっと待て
なぜ泣いている？
Wait!
Why are you crying?
謝りなさい
今すぐ漆原さんに
Apologize to Urushibara. Now.
No, seriously.
あ… いやいやいや
謝るも何も俺は真実しか…
Why would I apologize? It's true—
It's fine!
（るか）いいんです！
So that's what you think of me, Okabe.
僕…
岡部さんに そういうふうに
見られていたんですね
No, no, no, Rukako! You're really...
いやいやいや るか子
（岡部）お前は男だろ…
（紅莉栖）いつまで続ける気？
How long will you keep that up?
I'm going home!
（るか）僕 帰ります
待てっ！
Wait!
Stop messing around with me!
俺を担ぐのは よせ！
お前は正真正銘の男だ
You're a real guy!
Look! Right here, you have—
なぜなら ここに…
おっ？ ああっ…
（紅莉栖）はっ！
It's gone! There's nothing here!
（岡部）ない… ないぞ！
Okabe, stop it...
岡部さん…
やめて… くだ…
（鈴羽の鼻歌）
Rukako, you're a girl?
（岡部）るか子…
お前 女なのか？
最初から そう…
言っとるだろうがっ！
I've been saying that this whole time!
あっ
Yo! Uh, what's wrong?
（鈴羽）おーっす！
あっ どうかした？
Don't worry about it.
うっ 気にするな
軽く拷問を…
Just a bit of torture...
拷問？
まさか 牧瀬紅莉栖に？
Torture?
By Makise Kurisu?
Yes, but I've rectified the misunderstanding...
ああ　だが誤解は解けた
…はずだ
I think...
She got your legs?
足を攻められたの？
（岡部）どわああっ
今 足に触れてはならん
Don't touch my legs!
小一時間 正座をさせられ…
あっ ああっ　いや―
She made me sit on my knees for an hour!
No! I mean, I was tortured.
拷問を受けたあとなのだ
なんだ　そんなの
拷問のうちに入らないよ
Oh... That isn't torture.
You almost sound like you've been tortured.
まるで 本当の拷問を
受けたかのような口ぶりだな
そりゃあ 戦士だからね
Well, I am a warrior.
It's a perfect day for biking...
絶好のサイクリング日和だね
Yeah?
そうか？
Hey...
（鈴羽）あのさ…
Want to go for a ride?
ちょっと
サイクリングしない？
（岡部）ん？
（岡部の荒い息遣い）
Is this what you call biking?
（岡部）
これをサイクリングと―
言うのかっ？
I came to Tokyo to find my father.
（鈴羽）私さ
東京に来たのは 父さんを
捜索するためだったんだよね
（岡部）捜索？
蒸発でもしたのか？
To find him?
Did he disappear or something?
I haven't seen him in years.
（鈴羽）
もう何年も会ってなくて
顔も覚えていないんだ
I can't even remember his face.
この町にいることは
分かってるんだけどね
But I know he's in this city.
This is my only clue.
手がかりは これだけ
A badge he used to own.
父さんが持ってたピンバッチ
ならば のんきにバイトなど
している場合ではないだろう
Then you shouldn't waste time at a part-time job, should you?
There's some stuff going on, you know?
いろいろ事情があってね
でも 一度だけ
チャンスはあるんだ
But there's one chance.
えっ？
My dad might show up tomorrow at a certain place.
（鈴羽）あした ある場所に
父さんが現れるかもしれない
If I miss that chance, I'll have to leave this town.
それを逃したら 私はこの町を
離れなきゃいけないんだけどね
There's somewhere I have to go.
行かなきゃいけない所があるの
I'm a busy person, you know?
私も多忙なわけよ
Well, I always planned to give up if I couldn't meet him.
まあ もともと会えなかったら―
あきらめるつもりだったんだけどさ
（岡部）フッ…
You're worried, aren't you?
不安なのだな？
分かるぞ その気持ち
I know that feel.
だが しかし！
But that's too bad!
（鈴羽）おお…
Your luck ran out the minute
（岡部）
残念だったな バイト戦士よ
マッドサイエンティストである
この俺に相談したのが運の尽き
you spoke to the great mad scientist, Hououin Kyouma.
You are now Lab Member 008!
お前は 今日から
ラボメンナンバー００８だ！
You will be our guinea pig.
俺たちの
実験台となってもらう
Wh-What are you going to do?
（鈴羽）
ど… どうするの？
Change the past.
過去を変えるのだ
You may think me cruel if you like,
非道と思うなら思え
but there's no escape for you.
だが もはや逃れられぬ
Send a D-mail to your father before he leaves.
お前は蒸発する前の父親に
Ｄメールを送るのだ
Tell him not to leave his daughter behind.
“娘を置いて行くな”とな
フーッ ハッハッハッハッ
You're a good person, you know that?
（鈴羽）君って いいやつだね
（岡部）んっ なにっ？
What?
Somehow, I feel a bit better now.
なんか…
ちょっとだけ楽になったかも
そろそろ戻らなくちゃ
I have to get back.
Thanks for talking to me!
心配してくれて
サンキュー！
ああっ　いいか！
Listen!
Whether you see him tomorrow or not,
明日 父親に会えても会えなくても
必ずラボに来い
come by the lab!
I will use your sentimentality
（岡部）お前の傷心を利用し
Ｄメール実験をしてやる
for an experiment with the D-mail!
アハハハハッ
You really are a mad scientist!
（鈴羽）さすが
マッドサイエンティスト
悪逆非道だね アハハッ
That's terrible...
ハハハハッ
I will now explain the parameters of Operation Eldhrímnir.
（岡部）では
これより 作戦名―
「エルドフリームニル」の
概要について説明する
More Norse myths?
また北欧神話？
（岡部）
バイト戦士が父親に会えたなら
祝いの会―
If the part-time warrior meets her father,
we'll hold a celebration,
東京での最後の晩さんを
執り行う
a last supper in Tokyo, for her.
And if she doesn't, we'll try to cheer her up,
そして もし会えなかったときは
残念会
その後 Ｄメールの実験だ
and then send a D-mail.
Where's Daru?
あれ？ ダル君がいないよ？
He's meeting his online friends tonight,
今夜はオフ会があるから
参加できないなどと―
so he said he can't join us.
ふざけたことを言ってきた
The fool!
But I've taken steps.
だが すでに手は打ってある
To: Daru
Now is the time to choose
Feyris's cooking or your meeting.
Which will you choose?
I sent this message.
このメールを先ほど送っておいた
Feyris's cooking or your meeting.
（るか）“フェイリスの手料理と
オフ会 どっちを選ぶのだ？”
Which will you choose?
えーっ　だってフェリスちゃんは
来られないんでしょ？
But Feyris can't come, right?
Feyris has never met the part-time warrior,
フェイリスはバイト戦士と
面識はないのでしかたないが―
so it's pointless for her,
but Daru has a duty to participate in this operation.
ダルはこの作戦に
参加する義務がある
（るか）あの…
Um... I've never met this Suzuha person either.
僕も その鈴羽さんていう人には
会ったことないんですけど…
うん　かまわん
That's fine.
お前たちには
宴会用の買い出しに行ってもらう
I'm sending you all shopping for the banquet.
あんたは？
And you?
（岡部）バイト戦士を尾行し
状況を逐一報告する
I will follow the part-time warrior
and report in on the situation.
Don't you dare.
やめなさい　親子水入らずに
させてやりなさいよ
Let the father and daughter have their time together.
That's right.
そうだよ　オカリンも一緒に
買い出しに行こう？
Come shopping with us!
俺は尾行を…
I'm following—
I said no!
（紅莉栖）だから
ダメだっつってんでしょ！
助手の分際で
俺に指図する… ううっ
Don't tell me what to do, assistant...
Do you want to sit on your knees again?
また正座する？
今度は３時間ほど…
This time for three hours...
Now then! Let's get things ready for the party!
さて 宴会の準備を始めるか
（岡部）あっ？
ん？
I'm watching you.
ああっ…
What's wrong, Okarin?
どうしたの？ オカリン
Nothing.
（岡部）何でもない…
This is...?
（岡部）これは…
カレーは甘口がいいかな？
それとも辛口？
I think sweet curry will be nice.
Or maybe spicy?
What do you think?
どっちがいいと思う？
えっ？ あ… ああ
U-Uh... Spicy, I guess.
辛口でいいだろう
Oh, yeah! Suzu's a part-time warrior, right?
（まゆり）ああ そっか
鈴(すず)さんは
バイト戦士だもんね
戦士といったら
やっぱり辛口だよね
If she's a warrior, she'll want spicy.
Um... Next is the meat, the meat!
えーと　次は お肉 お肉
ほええ
Beef sure is expensive...
やっぱり牛肉は高いよ
Hey, Okarin.
ねえ オカリン？
You don't look good.
なんか元気ないよ？
Back there, you would've normally said...
さっきだって いつもなら―
"The Organization's interference has increased the price of beef!
“機関の妨害工作で
牛肉がとっても高い”
Has Operation Time Sale begun?", or something.
“オペレーションタイムセールは
まだか？”
…とか言ったりするのに
（岡部）フンッ！
But you need to use Norse mythology there, not "Time Sale."
そこは タイムセールではなく
北欧神話だ
It's me.
俺だ　機関の妨害により―
The Organization's interference has caused unexpected expenses in Operation Audhumbla.
オペレーションアウズンブラの
実行に予想外の出費が生じた
作戦資金の増額を要請する
I'm requesting additional funds for the operation.
ああ！ 一番星
The first sparkle!
Venus?
宵の明星か…
Hey, Okarin?
（まゆり）ねえ オカリン？
（岡部）ん？
Remember in elementary school
（まゆり）
オカリンって 小学生のころ―
when you got really sick with a high fever?
すごい熱出して
寝込んだことあったよね
Yeah, and the world was panicking over Y2K.
（岡部）ああ…
世間では2000年問題が
騒がれていた時期だったか
Mayushii was really scared you would die then.
あのときね―
まゆしぃは オカリンが
死んじゃうんじゃないかって―
すごく怖かったんだ
So, I prayed to the sky.
だからね お空に祈ってたの
And then, there was a shooting star.
そしたらね 流れ星が
ぴゅーって１つ…
I said to the shooting star,
まゆしぃは 流れ星に―
"Don't die, Okarin!" three times.
“オカリン死なないで”って
３回唱えたの
And the next day, you got better!
そしたら 次の日には
オカリンの熱が下がって―
目を覚ましたんだ
And so, I saved your life.
だから まゆしぃは
オカリンの命の恩人なんだよ
エヘヘ
No, that's not true.
いいや　違うな
あの状況で助かったのは
シュタインズ･ゲートの選択だ
It was the choice of Steins Gate that I survived back then.
ええーっ そうなの？
Was it?
そうなのだ
It was.
（まゆり）そっか
I see.
Hey, remember what you said,
ねえ 熱を出して倒れたとき―
when you got sick and collapsed?
オカリン
こんなこと言ったの覚えてる？
ん？
"Everything I saw began to flow together,
急に見ている物が
グニャグニャしてきて―
and suddenly, I began to shake and couldn't stand up."
立っていられなくて
フラフラして―
体がビクッとなったって…
You looked just like that
この前 フェリスちゃんの
マンションでも―
in Feyris's condominium.
オカリン
そんな感じだったんだよ
The feeling I had when I got that fever
（岡部）
熱を出して倒れたときの
あの感覚
was just like the feeling I get when I move world lines.
世界線を移動したときの感覚に
とても似ている
Which means...
…ということは―
I attained my magic eye, Reading Steiner,
魔眼(まがん)
リーディング･シュタイナーは―
at that moment?
まさに あのとき
この身に宿ったということか？
（まゆり）ただいま
We're back!
（るか）おかえりなさい
Welcome back.
んん？ なんか異臭がしないか？
Do you smell something weird?
多分 紅莉栖さんの作っている
アップルパイのにおいだと…
I think it's the smell of Kurisu's apple pie.
What?
なに？ これがか？
This?
Want Mayushii to help too?
まゆしぃも手伝おうか？
じゃあ 卵をゆでててくれる？
Can you boil an egg?
（まゆり）はーい
Sure!
ええっと…
Um... Can I use the Phone Microwave?
電話レンジ
使っていいかな？
ダ… ダメです
生卵を入れたら爆発しちゃいます
N-No!
If you drop a raw egg in, it'll explode!
卵は僕が…
I'll make the egg.
ええーっ
（紅莉栖）それじゃあ まゆりは
しいたけ刻んでおいて
Then you chop up the mushrooms, Mayuri.
Okay!
（まゆり）はーい
W-Wait!
ま… 待て！
You don't need mushrooms or boiled eggs for apple pie!
アップルパイに
しいたけも ゆで卵も必要なかろう
（紅莉栖）
つけ合わせのサラダに使うのよ
It's for the salad to go with it.
I don't think a boiled egg and mushroom salad really go with apple pie.
（岡部）いやいやいや…
アップルパイに―
しいたけと ゆで卵のサラダを
つけ合わせるのも―
（岡部）いかがなものか
（まゆり）とんとんとんとん
そこっ！
勝手にしいたけを刻むで…
And you,
stop chopping up mushrooms over there!
（紅莉栖）どいて どいて
Move!
うっ！ ぐっ…
It's me.
俺だ…
It seems I've released the seals that bound a dark god.
どうやら 邪神の封印を
解いてしまったらしい
If I don't contact you within the hour,
もし１時間以内に
連絡がなかったら―
両親に伝えてくれ―
tell my parents I loved them.
“愛していた”と…
Okabe, do you have a rice cooker?
（るか）岡部さん
炊飯器はありますか？
（橋田）フェイリスたんは？
フェイリスたんは いずこ？
Where's Feyris?
Hashida, you've been deceived.
橋田 あんた だまされてるわよ
Feyris said she couldn't come.
フェイリスさんは
来られないって言ってたから
ちょっ マジで？
おい オカリン！
Seriously?
Hey, Okarin!
Next time I get a chance, I'll take care of it.
（岡部）次の機会があったら
話はつけておく
Screw you!
（橋田）ふざけんなよ！
I was really looking forward to my time machine forum meeting.
せっかく
タイムマシン オフ会だったのに！
タイムマシン オフ会？
Time machine forum?
It's with a sci-fi message board I frequent a lot.
僕がよく見に行くＳＦ関係の
ＢＢＳのオフ会
A professional author was supposed to go too!
プロの作家も来る予定だったのに！
This is an interestingly shaped mess kit.
（るか）これ面白い形の
はんごうですね
（岡部）ああっ 触るな！
そいつは はんごうじゃない
Don't touch it.
That's not a mess kit.
It's Future Gadget #4, the Moad Snake.
未来ガジェット４号
「モアッドスネイク」だ
クレイモア地雷？
A claymore?!
…に模して作られた
超瞬間加湿器だ
It's made to look like one.
It's a super-instant humidifier.
Oh, this?
（るか）ああっ！ これか
（岡部）えっ？ や… やめろ！
（るか）えっ？
S-Stop! Don't!
（岡部）うわっ あっ
（紅莉栖･まゆり）
ああっ うわあっ
（橋田）ああっ
I'm sorry, Okabe.
（るか）
ごめんなさい 岡部さん
Don't worry about it.
（岡部）
過ぎたことは しかたがない
Next time, don't touch it.
次からは うかつに触るな
Hey, couldn't we use this?
（紅莉栖）ねえ
これ使えるんじゃない？
A vacuum cleaner?
（るか）掃除機… ですか？
Nope!
違うよ　未来ガジェット３号
It's Future Gadget #3.
Or #2?
あれ？ ２号だっけ？
#5!
（岡部）５号だ
And its name is
その名も“また つまらぬものを
つなげてしまった by五右衛門(ごえもん)”
"Once Again I've Connected Something Useless
by Goemon."
（橋田）
掃除機の排気をドライヤーの温風に
利用できるようにしたものだお
We made it so you can use a vacuum cleaner's output to warm a dryer.
Give it to me.
貸してみ
あっ 待て！
Wait!
When you use that, you need to turn off any other appliances, or...
それを使うときは 他の電化製品の
電源を切らなければ…
（一同）ああっ
...it'll trigger the breaker.
（岡部）ブレーカーが落ちる…
（まゆり）えーっ
Where's the flashlight?
懐中電灯どこだっけ
（るか）こ… これですか？
Is this it?
（橋田）
違う るか氏　それ大根
No, Miss Ruka.
That's a radish.
（まゆり）エヘヘ
U-Um, where's the breaker?
（紅莉栖）
えーと ブレーカーは…
If you walk around...
（岡部）おーい 動き回ると…
（紅莉栖）キャア
I told you...
（岡部）だから…
（紅莉栖）イッタタタ…
Ow...
The breaker's in the front hall.
（岡部）ブレーカーは玄関だ
（紅莉栖）ううっ…
Are you okay?
（岡部）大丈夫か？
（紅莉栖）フフフッ
フフフッ フフッ
What's so funny?
（岡部）何がおかしい！
（紅莉栖）
フフッ ごめんなさい
I'm sorry.
But...
でも…
（岡部）ん？
the lab I worked at in America had some of
（紅莉栖）私のいる
アメリカの研究所って―
the best people from around the world.
世界中から優秀な人たちが
集まってるんだけど―
みんなプライドが高くて
結構 殺伐としてるのよね
But they all had really huge egos,
so it was also a really hostile place.
Compared to them, your lab is really childish,
それに比べて あんたのラボは
幼稚だけど 居心地がいい
but it's a fun place to be.
（岡部）フッ…
I-I'm not praising you, okay?
（紅莉栖）別に
褒めてるわけじゃないからな
I was just kinda thinking that...
ただ 何となく
そう思っただけというか…
I guess maybe I simply wanted friends.
（岡部）俺は
友達が欲しかっただけなのかもな
I, um...
（紅莉栖）私は えっと…
I think of you as a companion.
仲間だと思ってるよ
（岡部）ん？
（紅莉栖）
前に言ってくれたでしょ？
You told me before, didn't you?
That I was your dear companion.
私のこと 大切な仲間だって
That made me really happy, I guess.
あれ 結構
うれしかったっていうか…
Do you have a fever?
（岡部）熱でもあるのか
N-No!
（紅莉栖）ね… ねえよ！
What? I'm trying to rethink my opinion of you...
何よ！ せっかく あんたのこと
見直してやってるのに
Stupid Okabe!
このバカ岡部！
（紅莉栖･岡部）はっ
（紅莉栖）あっ…
ふああーう…
（まゆり）鈴さん 遅いね
Suzu's late.
お父さんに会えたかな？
I wonder if she met her dad.
I bet they're finally spending time together.
今頃 水入らずの時間を
過ごしてるんじゃない？
I told her to come to the lab either way.
（岡部）
どちらにしても ラボには来いと
言ったはずなのだが
But it's late.
しかし
この時間では もう遅い
作戦は中止だ
お前たちは もう帰れ
We're aborting the operation.
You guys, go on home.
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
（岡部）やつめ！
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
Damn her!
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Does she plan to leave the city by herself?
（岡部）このまま 一人さみしく
この町を離れるつもりなのか？
I, Hououin Kyouma, will not allow that!
そんなことは
この鳳凰院凶真(ほうおういんきょうま)が許さん！
ハア ハア ハアッ
クソッ！
Damn it!
いったい どこに…
Where did she go?
ハッ
That's right...
そうだ
If I send a D-mail telling myself to follow her
Ｄメールを使って
今日の昼間の俺に―
no matter what this afternoon...
何があっても
鈴羽を尾行しろと…
だが―
But...
Is it okay for me to use D-mail
いいのか？
これ以上 Ｄメールを使っても
to change the past any more?
過去を改変してもいいのか？
（鈴羽）君って いいやつだね
You're a good person, you know that?
Somehow, I feel a bit better now.
なんか…
ちょっとだけ楽になったかも
I am the great mad scientist, Hououin Kyouma!
俺は狂気のマッドサイエンティスト
鳳凰院凶真
What do I have to fear?
何を恐れることが
あるというのだ！
フーッハッハッハッハッ
フッハッハッハッハッ
Do not give in to your assistant's threats.
（岡部）助手の脅迫に屈せず
Do not give in to your
assistant's threats. Follow Suzuha!
Follow Suzuha!
Do not give in to your
assistant's threats. Follow Suzuha!
ううっ…
（岡部）ううんっ
ハアッ！
ハアッ
Yo.
うーっす！
Good morning, part-time warrior.
おはよう バイト戦士
Slacking off?
サボり中か？
Last night, we were all up really late.
昨日は夜中まで
上で騒いでたからさ
I'm so tired.
すっごい眠いんだよね
Last night,
（岡部）
俺たちは 昨日の夜―
we had a last supper for you,
お前が父親に
会えなかったので―
実験台となってもらうための
最後の晩さんを開いた…
so you could be our guinea pig.
Right?
そうだな？
But the experiment never happened.
（鈴羽）
実験は出来なかったけどね
I don't know my dad's phone number.
父さんの携帯のアドレスが
分かんなかったから
I want to confirm something.
（岡部）１つ確認したいのだが…
How did I catch you?
俺は いったいどうやって
お前を確保した？
Were you drinking?
君 お酒飲んでた？
未成年のくせに ダメなんだぞ
You're underage. You shouldn't do that.
Just answer me.
いいから聞かせてくれ
Well, I was heading back from the time machine forum meeting...
えーっと 私が―
タイムマシン オフ会から
帰ろうとしたら…
Time machine forum?
タイムマシン オフ会？
That's where your dad was supposed to show up?
そこが―
父親の現れるかもしれないという
場所だったのか？
Yeah, my dad's calling himself Titor.
うん　私の父さんは
タイターって名乗ってるんだ
John Titor?!
（岡部）ジョン･タイターか？
Not John... Barrel.
ジョンじゃなくて バレル
Barrel Titor.
バレル･タイター
I told you that yesterday.
それも昨日 話したよね
Didn't you take a video of it on your phone?
君 携帯ムービー
撮ってなかったっけ？
あーあ　昨日は楽しかったな
Last night was so fun...
牧瀬紅莉栖さえいなければ
もっと楽しめたけどさ
It would've been more fun without Makise Kurisu, though.
あいつのアップルパイ
殺人的な まずさだったし…
Her apple pie was absolutely horrible.
But Urushibara Ruka's curry was great!
でも 漆原るかのカレーは
極上だった
Your lab's kinda nice, you know?
君たちのラボってさ
なんかいいね
みんなが仲良くて
いつも楽しそうで…
Everyone's friends, and you always seem to have fun.
I've never felt like I fit in so much anywhere else in my life.
あんな居心地のいい時間は
生まれて初めてだったよ
Then you're welcome anytime.
ならば 遠慮はいらん
Come whenever you like.
いつでも来ればいい
You're a lab member now.
お前は もうラボメンなのだ
うん
Yeah.
I'll try to search for my father a little more!
もうちょっとだけ―
頑張って
父さん捜してみるよ
～